

**Cláudio** Rodrigues

**DATE OF BIRTH:** 27/08/1998

#### **CONTACT**

**Nationality:** Portuguese, British

Gender: Male

Estrada de Santa Clara 295 A, null9300-163 Câmara De Lobos, Portugal

claudioduarterodrigues@gmai l.com

claudio.duarte.98@live.com.pt

(+351) 964039199

https:// www.claudiorodrigues.me/

Facebook: https:// www.facebook.com/ claudio.duarte.01/ LinkedIn: https:// www.linkedin.com/in/ cl%C3%A1udiorodrigues-5263551a8/

Other: https://github.com/

claudiorodr



#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm a computer science student form Portugal, I'm 21 years old, I'm an enthusiast of technology, specially everything software related. I have developed several open-source projects, either in my course or free time, most of them are available on my GitHub page with their description. Here you'll find more information about me, expertise, projects and people I've worked with. You can also use the contact form to send me a message, I'll try to respond as soon as possible.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

27/07/2018 - 20/08/2018 - Larvik, Norway

#### Waiter

Summer job at a family restaurant, involves the preparation of tables, serving food or beverages and taking payments.

Larvik, Norway

02/07/2019 - 02/08/2019 - Funchal, Portugal

### Mobile application developer

Marko Radeta

Summer internship collaboration with other members of an interdisciplinary team, including marine biologists from the Oceanic Observatory of Madeira, developing cross-platform mobile applications in order to collect and export dive data, for further analysis on migrations of marine species on the island of Madeira.

Professional, scientific and technical activities / <a href="https://www.m-iti.org">https://www.m-iti.org</a> / Caminho da Penteada, Polo Cientifico e Tecnologico da Madeira, floor -2, 9020-105, Funchal, Portugal

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

14/09/2016 - 28/06/2019 - Funchal, Portugal

#### **Bachlor's Degree**

University of Madeira

- Sistemas Operativos
- Programação Orientada a Objetos
- Sistemas Gestores de Bases de Dados
- Cálculo I
- Estrutura de Dados e Algoritmos
- Teoria e Fundamentos da Computação
- Arquitetura de Computação
- Introdução à Eletrónica
- Mecânica e Ondas
- Redes e Comunicação de Dados
- Sistemas Digitais
- Engenharia de Requisitos

#### Field(s) of study

Engineering, manufacturing and construction

EQF level 6 | https://www.uma.pt/

26/09/2020 - CURRENT - Funchal, Portugal

Master's Degree

Universidade da Madeira

https://www.uma.pt/

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Portuguese

**OTHER LANGUAGE(S):** 

**English** 

<b>Listening</b> C1	<b>Reading</b> B2	Spoken production B2	Spoken interaction C1	<b>Writing</b> B2
Norwegian  Listening  A2	<b>Reading</b> A1	Spoken production A1	Spoken interaction A1	<b>Writing</b> A2

## **DIGITAL SKILLS**

Python / JavaScript / Git / NodeJS / Django / Linux / Laravel / RESTful Api / MySQL

#### **DRIVING LICENCE**

Driving Licence: A1
Driving Licence: B1
Driving Licence: B

## **ORGANISATIONAL SKILLS**

## Organization skills

- Good control in planning and organizing tasks acquired in carrying out volunteering (MIUT).
- Good ability to detect and estimate errors, and learn from them.
- Good ability to manage and guide small teams acquired in carrying out various group work.
- Experience with working in small groups (2-3 people).

## COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

# Communication and interpersonal skills

- Good analytical and communication skills acquired through experience acquired as a waiter in Norway.
- Willing to teach and help colleagues with more difficulties.